tubularinsights.com 2019-12-15

# TubularInsights.com Privacy Policy

_Last Updated: May 30, 2017_

This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we receive through our websites (www.TubularLabs.com and other Tubular Labs URLs and websites) and our services, including without limitation our cross-platform video analytics and intelligence software platform. We will refer to all of our services and websites collectively as “Services.”  This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites, services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that, unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. So, please make sure that you have read and understand our [Terms of Service](https://tubularlabs.com/terms/).   By using our Services, you expressly consent to Tubular Labs’ collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with anything in this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Services.

## Revisions to this Privacy Policy

Any information that is collected via our Services is covered by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of those changes by posting them on the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll update the “Last Updated Date” above to indicate when those changes will become effective.

## How Do We Use the Information We Collect?

The short answer is that we generally use this information to provide and improve our Services, to generate statistics on how the Services are used, to administer your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), for marketing purposes, and to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate our Services.  Among other things, the information we collect can enable us to:

  * customize the content and analytic insights you see through the Services;
  * fulfill your requests for Services and validate your user rights
  * contact and communicate with you

## Information Collected from Tubular Labs Services

  *  **Automatic Collection:** Like most web businesses, we use automated mechanisms (e.g., Cookies and/or Web Beacons) to keep track of user interactions with our Services. “Cookies” are small text files that are placed on your device by a Web server when you access our Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that you’ve logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We may also use Cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent Cookies, session Cookies are deleted when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that if you don’t accept Cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services. Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also place their own Cookies on your device. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of Cookies and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties. “Web Beacons” (also known as Web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier that may be included on our Services for several purposes, including to deliver or communicate with Cookies, to track and measure the performance of our Services, to monitor how many visitors view our Services, and to monitor the effectiveness of our advertising. Unlike Cookies, which are stored on the user’s device, Web Beacons are typically embedded invisibly on web pages (or in an e-mail).  Our servers also automatically record certain information about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “Log Data”), including both Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “User”). Log Data may include information such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page that a User was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on our Services that a User clicked on and other statistics. We use Log Data to administer the Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) Log Data to improve, customize and enhance our Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s IP address to generate aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used. We also use third party services such as Mixpanel and Google Analytics to gather and analyze user information.
  *  **Volunteered:** If you open an Account with us, purchase products or services, send us an email, or share personal information with us in any other way, we collect this information. This obviously depends on what information you choose to provide but it may include your name, email address or billing information. You do not have to share this information with us, but without it you may not be able to access certain content, features or Services.
  *  **Posted:** If you post information on any public areas of our websites (or elsewhere on the Internet) that information may be collected and used by anyone, including Tubular Labs. (We strongly recommend that you do not post any information that allows strangers to identify or locate you. Posting such information may result in unsolicited and unwanted contact from others, to say the least.)
  *  **Authentication of Data from SNS Platforms:** Via the Settings section of your Account, you may choose to opt-in and allow Tubular Labs to connect to one (1) or more of your SNS Accounts (e.g. your Facebook Page or YouTube Channel) so that Tubular Labs may access data from the applicable SNS platforms on your behalf (such as dark posts and geo-fenced posts) (such data collectively, the “Authenticated Data”).  Tubular Labs may use Authenticated Data to improve the Services for you (e.g. by using such data to deliver a more accurate statistical data and rankings regarding your Facebook Page) and to improve the Services overall. Authenticated Data used to improve Tubular Labs’ Services will be aggregated and anonymized and used for purposes such as producing derived market estimations. Tubular Labs will not make your specific set of Authenticated Data available to Tubular Labs users other than on an aggregated and anonymized basis, unless you have chosen to opt-in to Tubular Labs’ Rank Booster Program. If you have opted into the Rank Booster Program (“Rank Booster Program”), Tubular Labs may make public some of your Authenticated Data, such as dark posts and geo-fenced posts, for the purpose of ensuring that all of your video activity is correctly attributed to you within Tubular Labs’ Services).  You may revoke Tubular Labs’ ability to collect your Authenticated Data at any time through the opt-out feature in the Settings section of your Account (see Your Choices below). In addition to opting out via the Settings section in your Tubular Labs Account, you may also revoke Tubular Labs’ access to YouTube Authenticated Data via the Google security settings page, found at: [https://secu](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions)[google.com/settings/security/permissions](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions). If you opt into authenticating any of your SNS Accounts with Tubular Labs, Tubular Labs will:
    * Never post on your behalf to any of your authenticated SNS Accounts (e.g. your Facebook Page or YouTube Channel).
    * Never manage any of your SNS Account ad campaigns (e.g. Facebook ad campaigns or YouTube ad campaigns) and will never alter any of your SNS ad settings.

If you have any questions or comments about SNS Authenticated Data, please email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3747455e4156544e77434255425b56455b5655441954585a).

## When Do We Share or Disclose Your Information?

  *  **Personally Identifiable Information.** In more limited circumstances, we may share personally identifiable information we have collected. For example:
    * We might share personally identifiable information during due diligence or in connection with a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation.
    * Your personal information may be transferred to anyone who is helping us make the Services available and functional, like technical agents, payment processing vendors, other subcontractors, and our affiliates and consultants.
    * As in any transaction, if you provide your credit card information to us for purchases, your credit card company will be provided with relevant information about us, services purchased, cost and other information necessary to process the transaction.
    * We may disclose your personal information if permitted or required by law, or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend our interests or the interests of our users or business partners.
    * We may share aggregated information and non-identifying information with third parties for industry research and analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes.

## Your Choices

  *  **Opt-Out.**
    * We may periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote our Services. When you receive such promotional communications from us, you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” (by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive). We do need to send you certain communications regarding the Services and you will not be able to opt out of those communications – e.g., communications regarding updates to our [Terms of Service](https://tubularlabs.com/terms/) or this Privacy Policy or information about billing.
    * You can opt-out of providing Authenticated Data to Tubular Labs at any time by revoking the permissions previously granted to Tubular Labs in the Settings section of your Account. Authenticated Data accessible by Tubular Labs during any ‘opt-in’ period in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
  *  **Modifying Your Information.** You can update or correct personal information (e.g., your email address) by accessing your Account. You can also access, or delete, your information by reaching out to us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b0c0c2d9c6d1d3c9f0c4c5d2c5dcd1c2dcd1d2c39ed3dfdd). We will respond to your request within 30 days. Please note that we have the right to reject deletion requests that are unduly burdensome or repetitive or that cannot be honored in light of legal obligations or ongoing disputes, or where retention is necessary to enforce our agreements or protect our or another party’s rights, property, safety, or security.

## Children Under 13

Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

## Third Parties

Like most websites, third parties may directly gather user information from users of our Services through automated means such as cookies. For example, companies who place ads on our websites may drop their own cookies on the computers of users who view their ads. This Privacy Policy does not cover how third parties gather and use such data.

In addition, the Services may contain links to third party websites and content. Tubular Labs does not control these websites and/or content and these third parties” privacy policies may be different from our own. You access linked websites or third party content at your own risk.

## Security

Any information collected by Tubular Labs is stored on servers that Tubular Labs manages, using standard security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information. Please be aware, however, that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and as a result, Tubular Labs cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit on or through the Services.

## Foreign Countries

Your personal information may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your country. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that Tubular Labs processes and stores information in the United States and your use of our Services constitutes your consent to and understanding of this processing.

## California Residents

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, also known as the “Shine the Light Law,” any of our users who are California residents are entitled to request and receive once a year, free of charge, a notice from us describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared, the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, and their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Tubular Labs Inc., 153 Castro Street #300, MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA 94041. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7f0f0d16091e1c063f0b0a1d0a131e0d131e1d0c511c1012).

You can also contact us by mail at Tubular Labs Inc., 153 Castro Street #300, MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA 94041

In addition, if you wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing, or if you would like to update or delete your email address, mailing address or other personal information, or otherwise manage communications you receive from Tubular Labs, please contact us at the above.
